[
    {
        "question": "Which airport is the opening scene of Love Actually set in?",
        "correctAnswer": "Heathrow",
        "answer1": "Gatwick",
        "answer2": "LAX",
        "answer3": "O'Hare",
        "answer4": "Heathrow"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country spans 11 time zones?",
        "correctAnswer": "Russia",
        "answer1": "The United States",
        "answer2": "China",
        "answer3": "Canada",
        "answer4": "Russia"
    },
    {
        "question": "Hamilton is the capital of which British Overseas Territory?",
        "correctAnswer": "Bermuda",
        "answer1": "Bermuda",
        "answer2": "New Zealand",
        "answer3": "Australia",
        "answer4": "Cayman Islands"
    },
    {
        "question": "In what city would you find Tiergarten?",
        "correctAnswer": "Berlin",
        "answer1": "Amsterdam",
        "answer2": "Vienna",
        "answer3": "Berlin",
        "answer4": "Zurich"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are there 270 of in the average human baby but only 206 in an adult?",
        "correctAnswer": "Bones",
        "answer1": "Nerves",
        "answer2": "Muscles",
        "answer3": "Bones",
        "answer4": "Facial wrinkles"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the first country to put a woman in space?",
        "correctAnswer": "The Soviet Union",
        "answer1": "The United States",
        "answer2": "The Soviet Union",
        "answer3": "The United Kingdom",
        "answer4": "India"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the lowest numbers on a roulette table?",
        "correctAnswer": "00",
        "answer1": "00",
        "answer2": "0",
        "answer3": "1",
        "answer4": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which country is Cusco located?",
        "correctAnswer": "Peru",
        "answer1": "Chile",
        "answer2": "Peru",
        "answer3": "Argentina",
        "answer4": "Cuba"
    },
    {
        "question": "What number is represented by \"C\" in Roman numerals?",
        "correctAnswer": "100",
        "answer1": "5",
        "answer2": "10",
        "answer3": "100",
        "answer4": "1000"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the least populous country in Africa?",
        "correctAnswer": "Seychelles",
        "answer1": "Mauritius",
        "answer2": "Comoros",
        "answer3": "Cape Verde",
        "answer4": "Seychelles"
    },
    {
        "question": "What does \"quid pro quo\" mean in English?",
        "correctAnswer": "Something for something",
        "answer1": "Seize the day",
        "answer2": "I think, therefore I am",
        "answer3": "Something for something",
        "answer4": "To the person"
    },
    {
        "question": "An astronomical unit is the standard measurement taken from the Earth to where?",
        "correctAnswer": "The Sun",
        "answer1": "The Moon",
        "answer2": "The Sun",
        "answer3": "Mars",
        "answer4": "Pluto"
    },
    {
        "question": "Pedophobia is the fear of what?",
        "correctAnswer": "Children",
        "answer1": "Pedophiles",
        "answer2": "Children",
        "answer3": "Parents",
        "answer4": "Police"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the rarest blood type",
        "correctAnswer": "AB-negative",
        "answer1": "O-negative",
        "answer2": "AB-positive",
        "answer3": "AB-negative",
        "answer4": "B-positive"
    },
    {
        "question (100)": "In the movie Good Will Hunting, what collehe does Skylar attend?",
        "correctAnswer": "Harvard",
        "answer1": "Harvard",
        "answer2": "Yale ",
        "answer3": "Colombia",
        "answer4": "Stanford",
        "question": "Which US state is known as the ''Sunflower state''?",
        "correctAnswer": "Kansas",
        "answer1": "Kansas",
        "answer2": "Oklahoma",
        "answer3": "Texas",
        "answer4": "California"
    },
    {
        "question": "What color were carrots originally?",
        "correctAnswer": "Purple",
        "answer1": "Orange",
        "answer2": "Brown",
        "answer3": "Yellow",
        "answer4": "Purple"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is a shrimp's heart?",
        "correctAnswer": "In its head",
        "answer1": "In its tail",
        "answer2": "In its head",
        "answer3": "Behind its eye",
        "answer4": "In its stomach"
    },
    {
        "question": "What body part does a fox use to communicate?",
        "correctAnswer": "Tail",
        "answer1": "Nose",
        "answer2": "Whiskers",
        "answer3": "Tail",
        "answer4": "Paws"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many times greater is a dog's hearing than a human's?",
        "correctAnswer": "10 times",
        "answer1": "2 times",
        "answer2": "It is not",
        "answer3": "5 times",
        "answer4": "10 times"
    },
    {
        "question": "What US state has the highest concentration of shopping malls?",
        "correctAnswer": "New Jersey",
        "answer1": "New Jersey",
        "answer2": "Texas",
        "answer3": "California",
        "answer4": "Indiana"
    },
    {
        "question": "What part of our body contains traces of gold?",
        "correctAnswer": "Hair",
        "answer1": "Bones",
        "answer2": "Blood",
        "answer3": "Hair",
        "answer4": "Muscles"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which country K2 mountain present?",
        "correctAnswer": "Pakistan",
        "answer1": "Pakistan",
        "answer2": "Nepal",
        "answer3": "China",
        "answer4": "India"
    },
    {
        "question": "A “crepuscular” animal becomes active at what time?",
        "correctAnswer": "Dusk",
        "answer1": "Dawn",
        "answer2": "Afternoon",
        "answer3": "Morning",
        "answer4": "Dusk"
    },
    {
        "question": "Atropos, Lachesis, and Clotho are the Three what of Greek mythology?",
        "correctAnswer": "Fates",
        "answer1": "Angels",
        "answer2": "Prophets",
        "answer3": "Fates",
        "answer4": "Signs of death"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was the only British Pope ever?",
        "correctAnswer": "Adrian IV",
        "answer1": "Gregory I",
        "answer2": "Adrian IV",
        "answer3": "Paul III",
        "answer4": "Leo X"
    },
    {
        "question": "Humphrey Bogart won his only Oscar for what motion picture?",
        "correctAnswer": "The African Queen",
        "answer1": "The Maltese Falcon",
        "answer2": "Sabrina",
        "answer3": "The African Queen",
        "answer4": "Casablanca"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the bloodiest battle of the American Civil War?",
        "correctAnswer": "Gettysburg",
        "answer1": "Gettysburg",
        "answer2": "Vicksburg",
        "answer3": "Sumter",
        "answer4": "Antietam"
    },
    {
        "question": "What famous actress once tried to hire a hitman to kill her?",
        "correctAnswer": "Angeline Jolie",
        "answer1": "Tilda Swinton",
        "answer2": "Angelina Jolie",
        "answer3": "Lindsey Lohan",
        "answer4": "Megan Fox"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which creatures produce gossamer?",
        "correctAnswer": "Spiders",
        "answer1": "Spiders",
        "answer2": "Bees",
        "answer3": "Ants",
        "answer4": "Crickets"
    },
    {
        "question": "The highest denomination bill ever printed in the United States was $100,000. Who was on the bill?",
        "correctAnswer": "Woodrow Wilson",
        "answer1": "Salmon P. Chase",
        "answer2": "Alexander Hamilton",
        "answer3": "Woodrow Wilson",
        "answer4": "William McKinley"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the pig leader in George Orwell’s Animal Farm?",
        "correctAnswer": "Napoleon",
        "answer1": "Snowball",
        "answer2": "Napoleon",
        "answer3": "Old Major",
        "answer4": "Boxer"
    },
    {
        "question": "What does the “E” stand for in the name of the American restaurant chain Chuck E. Cheese?",
        "correctAnswer": "Entertainment",
        "answer1": "Establishment",
        "answer2": "Eric",
        "answer3": "Entertainment",
        "answer4": "Everywhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "What bird can remember bad memories for up to 5 years?",
        "correctAnswer": "Kiwi",
        "answer1": "Ostrich",
        "answer2": "Kiwi",
        "answer3": "Hummingbird",
        "answer4": "Crow"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many vaginas do kangaroos have?",
        "correctAnswer": "3",
        "answer1": "1",
        "answer2": "2",
        "answer3": "3",
        "answer4": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was the first performer at the Woodstock festival in 1969?",
        "correctAnswer": "Richie Havens",
        "answer1": "Tim Hardin",
        "answer2": "Richie Havens",
        "answer3": "Joan Baez",
        "answer4": "Sweetwater"
    },
    {
        "question": "The penny-farthing was a popular type of what?",
        "correctAnswer": "Bicycle",
        "answer1": "Coin purse",
        "answer2": "Couch set",
        "answer3": "Bicycle",
        "answer4": "Bed frame"
    },
    {
        "question": "What island state was formerly known by the name Formosa?",
        "correctAnswer": "Taiwan",
        "answer1": "Sri Lanka",
        "answer2": "Taiwan",
        "answer3": "Barbados",
        "answer4": "Haiti"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country offered Einstein the presidency?",
        "correctAnswer": "Israel",
        "answer1": "Albania",
        "answer2": "Austria",
        "answer3": "Israel",
        "answer4": "Georgia"
    },
    {
        "question": "The cities of Xai-Xai, Panda, and Beira are in what country?",
        "correctAnswer": "Mozabique",
        "answer1": "Mozambique",
        "answer2": "China",
        "answer3": "Chad",
        "answer4": "Vietnam"
    },
    {
        "question": "What nationality was musician and composer James Last?",
        "correctAnswer": "German",
        "answer1": "British",
        "answer2": "Irish",
        "answer3": "German",
        "answer4": "Swedish"
    },
    {
        "question": "What year was the film \"The Fly\", starring Jeff Goldblum, released in theaters?",
        "correctAnswer": "1986",
        "answer1": "1991",
        "answer2": "1982",
        "answer3": "1980",
        "answer4": "1986"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal was part of the Gloria Vanderbilt jeans logo?",
        "correctAnswer": "Swan",
        "answer1": "Tiger",
        "answer2": "Horse",
        "answer3": "Swan",
        "answer4": "Lizard"
    },
    {
        "question": "What color were the first taxis in America?",
        "correctAnswer": "Green and red",
        "answer1": "Yellow and black",
        "answer2": "Green and red",
        "answer3": "Blue and black",
        "answer4": "Red and white"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which U.S. president was the first to leave the country while in office?",
        "correctAnswer": "Theodore Roosevelt",
        "answer1": "Woodrow Wilson",
        "answer2": "William McKinley",
        "answer3": "James A. Garfield",
        "answer4": "Theodore Roosevelt"
    },
    {
        "question": "What sort of meat is used in the dish \"Guard of Honour\"?",
        "correctAnswer": "Lamb",
        "answer1": "Lamb",
        "answer2": "Beef",
        "answer3": "Pork",
        "answer4": "Duck"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who did the Austrian army attack in the Battle of Karánsebes?",
        "correctAnswer": "Itself",
        "answer1": "Germany",
        "answer2": "Itself",
        "answer3": "Poland",
        "answer4": "The Netherlands"
    },
    {
        "question": "What US state is also known as the Volunteer State?",
        "correctAnswer": "Tennessee",
        "answer1": "Texas",
        "answer2": "Oklahoma",
        "answer3": "Tennessee",
        "answer4": "California"
    },
    {
        "question": "A \"Tiny Tim\" is a variety of what fruit?",
        "correctAnswer": "Snoopy",
        "answer1": "Charlie Brown",
        "answer2": "Snoopy",
        "answer3": "Popeye",
        "answer4": "Flash Gordon"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who hit .202 with three homers while playing outfield for the Birmingham Barons in 1994?",
        "correctAnswer": "Michael Jordan",
        "answer1": "Karl Malone",
        "answer2": "Charles Barkley",
        "answer3": "Michael Jordan",
        "answer4": "David Robinson"
    },
    {
        "question": "What bird is Britain's VTOL \"jump jet\" named for?",
        "correctAnswer": "Harrier hawk",
        "answer1": "Red kite",
        "answer2": "Osprey",
        "answer3": "Merlin",
        "answer4": "Harrier hawk"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Egyptian plover is a bird best known for its symbiotic relationship with what host animal?",
        "correctAnswer": "Crocodile",
        "answer1": "Crocodile",
        "answer2": "Camel",
        "answer3": "Cat",
        "answer4": "Snake"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which US President was known as \"the peanut president\"?",
        "correctAnswer": "Jimmy Carter",
        "answer1": "George H. Bush",
        "answer2": "Lyndon B. Johnson",
        "answer3": "Jimmy Carter",
        "answer4": "Gerald Ford"
    },
    {
        "question": "What 1950's rock pioneer was portrayed by Lou Diamond Phillips in a 1987 film?",
        "correctAnswer": "Ritchie Valens",
        "answer1": "Buddy Holly",
        "answer2": "Ritchie Valens",
        "answer3": "Elvis Presley",
        "answer4": "Gene Vincent"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which scientist is credited with being the first one to isolate DNA material in 1869?",
        "correctAnswer": "Friedrich Miescher",
        "answer1": "Francis Crick",
        "answer2": "Maurice Wilkins",
        "answer3": "Oswald Avery",
        "answer4": "Friedrich Miescher"
    },
    {
        "question": "What Jewish custom was adopted by Southern Americans for the New Year?",
        "correctAnswer": "Eating black-eyed peas",
        "answer1": "Lighting 101 candles",
        "answer2": "Melting tin to read fortunes",
        "answer3": "Eating black-eyed peas",
        "answer4": "Drinking mulled wine"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which Beatles song is partially in French?",
        "correctAnswer": "Michelle",
        "answer1": "Eleanor Rigby",
        "answer2": "Hey Jude",
        "answer3": "All my loving",
        "answer4": "Michelle"
    },
    {
        "question": "Mead is made primarily from what?",
        "correctAnswer": "Honey",
        "answer1": "Mashrooms",
        "answer2": "Sugarcane",
        "answer3": "Honey",
        "answer4": "Apple juice"
    },
    {
        "question": "What year did Cambodia declare its independence from France?",
        "correctAnswer": "1953",
        "answer1": "1962",
        "answer2": "1975",
        "answer3": "1949",
        "answer4": "1953"
    },
    {
        "question": "At what popular Seattle market did Starbucks open its first store in 1971?",
        "correctAnswer": "Pike place",
        "answer1": "Oxbow ",
        "answer2": "Pike place",
        "answer3": "Chattanooga",
        "answer4": "West side"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the traditional gift for a 40th wedding anniversary?",
        "correctAnswer": "Ruby",
        "answer1": "Diamond",
        "answer2": "Gold",
        "answer3": "Ruby",
        "answer4": "Emerald"
    },
    {
        "question": "How did the Snickers bar get its name?",
        "correctAnswer": "After a horse",
        "answer1": "After village in England",
        "answer2": "After a summer festival",
        "answer3": "After toy company",
        "answer4": "After a horse"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who directed the film \"The Silence of the Lambs\"?",
        "correctAnswer": "Johnathan Demme",
        "answer1": "Ridley Scott",
        "answer2": "Stephen Spielberg",
        "answer3": "Johnathan Demme",
        "answer4": "David Lynch"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the full name of writer H. G. Wells?",
        "correctAnswer": "Herbert George Wells",
        "answer1": "Harry Gilbert Wells",
        "answer2": "Herbert George Wells",
        "answer3": "Henry Griffin Wells",
        "answer4": "Holden Gregory Wells"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the Roman name of the Greek god Hermes?",
        "correctAnswer": "Mercury",
        "answer1": "Pluto",
        "answer2": "Mars",
        "answer3": "Mercury",
        "answer4": "Saturn"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which German city did Joseph Stalin, Winston Churchill and President Franklin D Roosevelt meet in 1945?",
        "correctAnswer": "Potsdam",
        "answer1": "Munich",
        "answer2": "Cologne",
        "answer3": "Düsseldorf",
        "answer4": "Potsdam"
    },
    {
        "question": "What sporting event is also called \"birling\"?",
        "correctAnswer": "Log rolling",
        "answer1": "Log rolling",
        "answer2": "Bowling",
        "answer3": "Pool",
        "answer4": "Wife carring"
    },
    {
        "question": "What sporting legend is nicknamed \"The Great One\"?",
        "correctAnswer": "Wayne Gretzky",
        "answer1": "Lebron James",
        "answer2": "Michael Jordan",
        "answer3": "Wayne Gretzky",
        "answer4": "Tom Brady"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the common name for CH3COOH?",
        "correctAnswer": "Acetic acid",
        "answer1": "Deoxyribonucleic acid",
        "answer2": "Ribonucleic acid",
        "answer3": "Phospholipids",
        "answer4": "Acetic acid"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which city has been awarded the most total Michelin stars as of 2020?",
        "correctAnswer": "Tokyo",
        "answer1": "Tokyo",
        "answer2": "New York",
        "answer3": "Paris",
        "answer4": "Singapore"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the scientific name of the \"western lowland gorilla\"?",
        "correctAnswer": "Gorilla gorilla gorilla",
        "answer1": "Pan troglodytes",
        "answer2": "Gorilla gorilla gorilla",
        "answer3": "Pongo pygmaeus",
        "answer4": "Macaca"
    },
    {
        "question": "Nelis, Seckel, Forelle and Bosc varieties of what?",
        "correctAnswer": "Pears",
        "answer1": "Pears",
        "answer2": "Apples",
        "answer3": "Peaches",
        "answer4": "Mangos"
    },
    {
        "question": "When did the Panama Canal open?",
        "correctAnswer": "1914",
        "answer1": "1892",
        "answer2": "1914",
        "answer3": "1922",
        "answer4": "1905"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Winter Olympics Games were first held in which country?",
        "correctAnswer": "France",
        "answer1": "France",
        "answer2": "Sweden",
        "answer3": "Italy",
        "answer4": "Germany"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which war was ended by the \"Peace of Westphalia\"?",
        "correctAnswer": "Thirty Year's War",
        "answer1": "World War I",
        "answer2": "Seven Year's War",
        "answer3": "Thirty Year's War",
        "answer4": "War of the Oranges"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many engines are on a B-52 bomber?",
        "correctAnswer": "Eight",
        "answer1": "Eight",
        "answer2": "Five",
        "answer3": "Four",
        "answer4": "Ten"
    },
    {
        "question": "Mt. Elbrus, the tallest peak in Europe, is located where?",
        "correctAnswer": "Russia",
        "answer1": "Austria",
        "answer2": "Germany",
        "answer3": "Russia",
        "answer4": "France"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the sequel to \"Little Women\"?",
        "correctAnswer": "Good Wives",
        "answer1": "Jo's Boys",
        "answer2": "Little Boys",
        "answer3": "Under the Lilacs",
        "answer4": "Good Wives"
    },
    {
        "question": "The popular tourist destination, Amalfi, is located in which Italian region?",
        "correctAnswer": "Campania",
        "answer1": "Campania",
        "answer2": "Umbria",
        "answer3": "Marche",
        "answer4": "Piemonte"
    },
    {
        "question": "What city was the first American college located in?",
        "correctAnswer": "Cambridge",
        "answer1": "Philadelphia",
        "answer2": "New Heaven",
        "answer3": "Cambridge",
        "answer4": "Hamilton"
    },
    {
        "question": "What did France give to Vassar College at the end of World War I?",
        "correctAnswer": "A tank",
        "answer1": "A tank",
        "answer2": "A plane",
        "answer3": "A collection of uniforms",
        "answer4": "A helicopter"
    },
    {
        "question": "What author created Utopia?",
        "correctAnswer": "Thomas More",
        "answer1": "Aldous Huxley",
        "answer2": "Thomas More",
        "answer3": "John Locke",
        "answer4": "Francis Bacon"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was awarded the Nobel Peace Prize in 1973?",
        "correctAnswer": "Henry Kissinger",
        "answer1": "Henry Kissinger",
        "answer2": "René Cassin",
        "answer3": "Norman Borlaug ",
        "answer4": "Chancellor Willy Brandt "
    },
    {
        "question": "Badlands National Park is located in which U.S. state?",
        "correctAnswer": "South Dakota",
        "answer1": "North Dakota",
        "answer2": "Montana",
        "answer3": "Virginia",
        "answer4": "South Dakota"
    },
    {
        "question": "What Egyptian pharaoh was known as \"The Boy King\"?",
        "correctAnswer": "Tutankhamen",
        "answer1": "Khufu",
        "answer2": "Djoser",
        "answer3": "Tutankhamen",
        "answer4": "Ramses II"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the first full feature film directed by George Lucas?",
        "correctAnswer": "THX 1138",
        "answer1": "Star Wars",
        "answer2": "THX 1138",
        "answer3": "American Graffiti",
        "answer4": "Kagemusha"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which epic film was based on a novel by Lew Wallace?",
        "correctAnswer": "Ben Hur",
        "answer1": "Ben Hur",
        "answer2": "Spartacus",
        "answer3": "Once Upon a Time in The West",
        "answer4": "The Longest Day"
    },
    {
        "question": "Shu was an Egyptian God of what?",
        "correctAnswer": "Air",
        "answer1": "Water",
        "answer2": "Fire",
        "answer3": "Sun",
        "answer4": "Air"
    },
    {
        "question": "What country was formerly known as Abyssinia?",
        "correctAnswer": "Ethiopia",
        "answer1": "Ghana",
        "answer2": "Mali",
        "answer3": "Chad",
        "answer4": "Ethiopia"
    },
    {
        "question": "What screen legend made his final appearance in the movie \"The Harder They Fall\"?",
        "correctAnswer": "Humphrey Bogart",
        "answer1": "Marlon Brando",
        "answer2": "Paul Newman",
        "answer3": "Humphrey Bogart",
        "answer4": "Cary Grant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which cartoon character was created by Max Fleischer in the 1930's?",
        "correctAnswer": "Betty Boop",
        "answer1": "Scrappy",
        "answer2": "Betty Boop",
        "answer3": "Pop Eye",
        "answer4": "Cat Tom"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was the first king of Norway?",
        "correctAnswer": "Harald Fairhair",
        "answer1": "Harald Fairhair",
        "answer2": "Eric Bloodaxe",
        "answer3": "Haakon the Good",
        "answer4": "Harald Greycloak"
    },
    {
        "question": "Wild Turkey is what kind of alcohol?",
        "correctAnswer": "Bourbon",
        "answer1": "Scotch",
        "answer2": "Bourbon",
        "answer3": "Gin",
        "answer4": "Vodka"
    },
    {
        "question": "What would a tailor measure in lignes?",
        "correctAnswer": "Buttons",
        "answer1": "Shoe laces",
        "answer2": "Shirt sleeves",
        "answer3": "Button",
        "answer4": "Wrists"
    },
    {
        "question": "What horror movie was based on the novel \"Ratman's Notebooks\"?",
        "correctAnswer": "Willard",
        "answer1": "Black Christmas",
        "answer2": "Willard",
        "answer3": "Of Unknow Origin",
        "answer4": "Final Destination"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which country did the Mambo dance originate?",
        "correctAnswer": "Cuba",
        "answer1": "Argentina",
        "answer2": "Jamaica",
        "answer3": "Cuba",
        "answer4": "Costa Rica"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who created the original Star Trek series?",
        "correctAnswer": "Gene Roddenberry",
        "answer1": "Alex Kurtzman,",
        "answer2": "Gene Roddenberry",
        "answer3": "Hal Sutherland",
        "answer4": "Rick Berman"
    },
    {
        "question": "If you are at Chicago's Comiskey Park, what sport would you be watching?",
        "correctAnswer": "Baseball",
        "answer1": "Baseball",
        "answer2": "Basketball",
        "answer3": "Football",
        "answer4": "Ice Hockey"
    },
    {
        "question": "Jenny and Linn Berggren are singers with which 1990's group?",
        "correctAnswer": "Ace of Base",
        "answer1": "TLC",
        "answer2": "Spice Girls",
        "answer3": "Ace of Base",
        "answer4": "All Saints"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the last letter added to the English alphabet?",
        "correctAnswer": "J",
        "answer1": "Y",
        "answer2": "Q",
        "answer3": "W",
        "answer4": "J"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is television chef Rachael Ray's signature phrase?",
        "correctAnswer": "Yum-O",
        "answer1": "Yummy-O",
        "answer2": "Food O'Clock",
        "answer3": "Yum-O",
        "answer4": "Tummy Slappin'"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of Juliet's cousin killed by Benvolio in \"Romeo and Juliet\"?",
        "correctAnswer": "Tybalt",
        "answer1": "Mercutio",
        "answer2": "Tybalt",
        "answer3": "Benvolio",
        "answer4": "Gregory"
    }
]
